The End of the Sea
Did you know there's an awesome
treasure hidden at the end of the sea?
And anyone who finds it,
the King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
Bon voyage!
Have the courage that sail and believe,
and we will see a glimpse of
the sun rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons,
sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now,
for together we found we looked
through the spyglass and see.
And we know that our hearts
have brought us here,
where the conscious point's our destiny.
There's no looking back,
take the hell with me!
Bon voyage, we can't
stop all our troubles!
Forget the past.
Though the future's
unclear, we still can smile.
We know we'll get there, no regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only helps.
Our dreams come true!
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow?
Quite the gathering!
How many players remain
in our little game?
We have four Divine Squad members,
and since I dealt the wounds
I dealt those two were fatal,
that leaves us with four Shandians
and one Blue Sea-Dweller?
counting the Lord of the Sky and Holy.
That's ten people and two animals.
You will pay for harming Wiper!
Is that so?
You'd willingly forfeit your
life for this sad speck,
mind who you throw your
loyalty to, Savage.
Enough of this.
Holy, it's time for your mad dash.
Don't stop! Finish it!
He's building some kind of fence.
Damn, he's using more of his tricks.
This could be trouble.
No tricks here.
Behold the ordeal of iron.
The white barbed deathmatch has begun.
so you can put up a fence big
deal i wasn't planning to run the
purpose of this barrier isn't just
to hold you yes there's a reason
it's called white barbs what's
that i
guess the
thorns are painful
thanks for So how do I get out of
here once I'm done with all of you?
You can worry about that
later, assuming you survive.
Only eight people and two animals left.
Wiper!
Huh?
Wiper! Listen!
Lucky.
Quickly!
There isn't much time! What's wrong?
Why are you here?
I had to come to give
you Kamakiri's warning!
Nobody can beat Enaru.
You must run away!
Abandon this fight!
Enaru.
He's in the forest.
Enough.
Eneru is lightning itself.
He truly has the powers of a god.
Stop.
Leave at once.
He cannot be defeated.
Do as I say.
Wiper?
Did I hear my name?
Eneru
Enneru, leave her be!
Lockie's not here to fight!
I'm the one you want!
Lock, run!
You're a fool!
I'd forget about her and
worry more about myself!
Lock, no!
Run!
He can't be conquered.
You've sealed your fate, Wiper.
You damn fool.
Please survive.
Anna Ru.
You should be writhing in pure agony.
Let's try that again.
You didn't actually
think I'd spare her wiper
the ruthless Shandora warrior surely you
Understand the concept
of no mercy she opposed
me and now she's dead
you'll join her soon enough
That's him.
That's God?
Weep not for her.
She is free.
Since we're all getting personal,
there's a score I have to settle as well.
The Snake!
Time to cough up what's in your belly!
Get out of my way!
Holy!
They need a hug!
Ice and whip!
The numbers dwindle.
Six people and two animals remain.
Good sign.
Where in the world is this place
we got swallowed up? Remember? Ah.
Ah, yes, of course.
The beast seems even
larger from the inside.
Isa, are you okay?
Wiper, please forgive me!
What happened?
Right, for the umpteenth time,
we've been eaten by a snake.
A snake?!
Calm down, we'll survive.
If we can escape before it digests us.
What were you two doing out there you should
be on the ship tell that to the Creeps
who were chasing us we had to run for our
lives isn't that little girl a Shandora
Just calm down anyway why don't we simply
carve our way out are you
insane old man Suppose
the snake starts going wild you're gonna
get us all killed you
know For a night you're
pretty dense by y 'all
was kidding we're in
a stomach a snake's
stomach I don't know how
much you know about
anatomy but it won't be
long before we're bathing
in its metabolic acid
It's you
Luffy I was starting to think
I was the only one here.
Isn't this the strangest cave
That's an understatement.
How'd you end up here?
I don't know.
I just got stuck here and I can't get out.
Incredible.
This snakes turning out
to be a serious problem.
A snake who'd you think
this stomach belong to.
But how could you be here talking to me if
you were swallowed by
a giant snake like I?
I said, big blue reptile
with my long fangs!
It ate it and now we're
stuck in his belly!
Oh, come on Nami, that hurts.
Hi, I'm Usa.
Is he a jester?
That job would suit him best,
but he's actually captain.
He's your captain?
My word.
What's this world coming to?
You sure are calm for someone
who's been eaten by a monster
It's stomach acid is melting your clothes
Whoa, you're right
What are we waiting for we need to
find its butthole right away ridiculous
Why maybe we can get out next time
the snake goes to the bathroom
No!
I'd rather get digested!
Nami's scary.
I know what you mean, child.
She's meaner than the snake.
Hardly, when the snake gets in a
bad mood, it starts eating people.
And speaking of which,
we'd better think fast.
Its temper was wild enough on the outside.
Wait, the snake was in a bad mood?
Luffy, what have you been doing in here?
Oh, I was trying to bust through
a wall didn't work though.
Ah,
so this is all you're doing throwing all
those punches burned up a lot of energy?
Sam did any of you think
to bring some food?
What's wrong?
How about you eat my
What's the matter, got a bellyache?
It serves you right!
It won't be long, Isa! Hold on!
Open up, Serpent!
This is getting really old.
That extendable sword is using as a
pain and that snake I already know.
Defeating him first isn't exactly
going to be a walk in the park.
But I have to get Nami and the old
knight out of that thing's gut right now.
There's still time.
Since they were swallowed hollow.
and bet they're not dead yet, but
it won't be that way for long.
IZENWHIP!
Not again!
That bastard, where is he?
IZENWHIP!
Huh?
How come he always knows
exactly where I am?
It's as if he could see
me from behind that wall.
Who is this madman?
What's up with those glasses?
Now prepare to die!
This has nothing to do with you.
Another voice has disappeared.
There are only a few survivors
in the upper ruins now.
Just five people and two animals remain.
I'm wrong.
Make that four people.
Park wave guys in back.
An iron wall?
This sword is an iron cloud.
You didn't think clouds had
a set shape, did you? You?
Aizen fan!
Aizen fork!
Aizen rapier pack!
He's predicting my movements,
why can't I avoid it?
What's the matter?
Keeping your distance doesn't do you
any good when you depend on your sword.
You're wrong about that.
36 Caliber Phoenix!
Arsene Witt!
How could he block it?
That's quite an interesting technique
you've developed, Blue Sea Dweller.
Who wonder if you'll try that again?
Unfortunately even if you lose sight
of me I'll always know where you are.
By using mantra
looks
like
we just lost another one.
Now there are two animals
and three people left but
soon there will be two
animals and only two people.
So you're the leader of the
blue sea people up here?
You and your comrades
I'll put up a good fight.
However my sword is now
pointed directly at your heart.
Say your prayers.
Swordsman don't be an idiot.
I never pray for anything that's too bad.
You should use your resources.
I don't have to see you.
I can follow that extendable sort of
yours and know exactly where you are.
Well the moment you find
you die.
One life holds 36 worldly desires.
Two lives hold 72.
Three lives hold 108 worldly
desires.
Three swords, 108 caliber Phoenix.
We broke through the iron clouds.
No!
Huh? No!
Huh?
Anyone?
In that case, just knock
yourself unconscious.
Gotta hurry and take care of
that snake and the bazooka guy.
Shandora, the City of Gold.
And if the Golden Bell said to be in the
middle of the city isn't here, where is it?
The belfry was probably
engraved with poneglyphs.
If that's the case, then the city
probably fell in order to protect them.
Even after all this time, the Belfry
and the Poneglyph should still be here.
They're hidden, somewhere.
Hey, what's that?
A rail used to run through this city
But this is new something
was moved out of here.
I wonder what it was
Isn't it amazing even after
being shot up into the sky
the city of Shandora still
majestically exists in this way
Even if it's a city that
everyone knows about,
how can it show off its
lovely figure if it's
covered by clouds?
I'm the only one who could see it.
I discovered it.
The former gods never
even noticed.
And who are you?
I'm God.
You're quite intelligent.
One might Guess that
you're an archaeologist
from the blue sea world
by how fast you found.
The city of ruins it took
us several months to find.
The same thing I suppose it's easier if you
Can read the letters on the ruins right.
Unfortunately the gold you're
looking for isn't Here anymore.
I'm afraid you're a few
years too late for that.
The gold well you're right
about That I couldn't find any.
You must have been the one who removed it.
Gold is a wonderful thing to Have and
that glittering metal suits me well.
Don't you think?
Then you must also Have taken the
golden bell that was once here. Hmm.
There was a golden bell.
He doesn't know.
Well I'm very intrigued.
What did you learn by reading
those letters on the bell?
Actually, it's too bad.
I never got to read them.
If you say it wasn't here when
you arrived, it must not exist.
I guess the huge golden bell
and belfry that were the
pride of Shandora must have
only been another legend.
It's a shame that I'll never
be able to lay my eyes on them.
No, wait. It's...
it's actually right here.
It's here in the sky.
When this island was blown into the sky
400 years ago when the Upper Yard was born.
Or when Godland was born,
it was said that the loud
chimes of a bell could
be heard ringing throughout
the entire nation.
The elder inhabitants of this land
called it the island's singing voice.
But that wasn't it.
It was the bell.
The bell made of gold.
Amazing soon the entire game will be over
only eight minutes left
That's not long at all.
In fact, it gives me plenty of
time to look for the Golden Bell
So the Golden Bell is in the sky,
which means the poneglyphs are too.
Interesting it sounds like
there's a maggot on the island?
What's the matter with you,
Sue, did we forget to see you?
Sue, are you in pain,
or did something happen?
Are you?
Yes, I'm one of the men who used to
serve God and fall when he was God.
So you're one of the divine warriors?
We were in a closed off area and then...
Goodness, what on earth happened to you?
Conis, he needs your help right away.
Yes, of course, Father.
No, wait.
My family's on Angel Island.
Please, please help. I will.
I know everyone's
worried about all of you.
Let everyone know, Anaru.
He's planning to return everything. What?
Skybia will be dropped back
into the Blue Sea World,
and this entire nation
will no longer exist.
But that can't be true.
There's no time to lose you
must tell everyone do it now.
Our lives will soon be
over and a room is planning
to eliminate every living
person from the sky.
Eliminate everyone from the sky but
wait if he succeeds in that then?
He won't have a place to live.
It doesn't make any sense.
Why would he want to do that?
He built a ship, the Ark Maxim.
Ark Maxim?
Hey, what are you...
We were forced to spend the last six
years of our lives building that ship!
Father!
When the sky finally becomes peaceful,
I'd like to be able to show everyone the
hospitality they once knew
to my heart's content,
including you.
Father!
What exactly did you just do?
Hm.
I showed mercy.
This man...
he has Logia power.
And now, I must say what little time
we have left here is coming to a close.
This is the beginning of the end.
I will now set into motion a series of
events that will reveal my ultimate plan.
What plan? What do you mean?
The Sky Lord is calling you!
Heed my call, lonely
beings, and come to me!
Snake!
What the...
What are you doing?
It was I who brought you and
your friends here to Shandora.
I beckoned you.
I've never seen anything like this before.
This man possesses such tremendous power.
The whole place has brought me apart.
What?
It's Anaru.
He's the only one who's powerful
enough to do something like this.
I'd better think of something.
Huh? Jumper!
What's that?
There's a hole at the base.
And now this brings us
to our climactic finale!
I suggest we attempt
our escape now! Right!
Yeah, it's now or never!
Luffy, get over here and
grab hold of the Waver!
I'm gonna finally get
us out of this snake!
Right!
Hey you, hang on to me!
Here we go!
Yay!
I can't wait to get out!
Man overboard!
We can't leave them!
Pierre, go back!
You have to save those two!
How I'll pick it up so high?
I have no idea!
Mia, Mia, don't worry about me,
you'll have to save the others! Mia!
So what are we gonna do now that
the bird's gone, you weird old man?
My name's Gonbe, it's Gonbe!
I don't care, just save us!